(Maitre d':)Well, you know, Valentine's Day.
Yes. Oh,
(Penny:)bet your girlfriend is super
bummed you had to work tonight.
(Penny:)Anyway, look, we have been
waiting a while,
(Penny:)and I just...
With all
(Maitre d':)due respect, ma'am,
there's nothing I can do.
(chuckles)
You don't have to call me ma'am.
(Amy:)Okay.
I mean,
(Penny:)we're basically the same age.
(laughs):
Okay.
(Penny:)How old are you?
(Maitre d':)I'm 21. How old are you?
(Penny:)Just shut up, Glen.
(Penny:)Come on, let's get out of here.
(Leonard:)What? Why?
Because I'm young. Let's go.
(Raj(on phone):)Rajesh,
it's perfectly normal
(Amy:)to have doubts
after breaking up with someone.
Well, you really think so?
(Sheldon:)Yeah, you know
what's not normal?
(Sheldon:)Blubbering about emotions
during a flag show.
(Sheldon:)Unless that emotion is
excitement over New Zealand
(Sheldon:)changing their flag.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, good luck, you crazy
Kiwis, we're rooting for you.
(Amy:)Your friend is hurting.